localjobster.com 2013-11-29

# Local Jobster - Find Local Jobs Online

Effective Date: January 26, 2011 

This Privacy Policy governs your use of this web site and any content, products or services made available from or through this website including any sub domains thereof ("Web Site"). The Website is made available by LocalJobster.com, hereafter referred to as ("Company"). By visiting this Web Site and requesting information, products or services offered on or through this Web Site, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy, as they may be amended from time to time. As Company updates or expands its Web Site, services or products, this Privacy Policy may change and the changes are effective upon posting. Please check back frequently for updates as it is your sole responsibility to be aware of changes. Company does not provide notice of changes in any manner other than by posting the changes at this Web Site. This Privacy Policy is incorporated into, and part of, the Web Site Terms and Conditions of use ("Terms of Use"), which governs your use of this Web Site in general. This Web Site is intended for users who are located in the United States of America. The Privacy Policy shall be interpreted under the laws of the United States. 

### Purpose of the Privacy Policy.

The purpose of this Policy is to describe the information collection, use, and dissemination practices of LocalJobster.com, its parent, subsidiaries and registered d/b/a companies (Collectively Referred herein after as "Company") and all related websites owned or registered to Company and applies to Company's collection, use, storage and disclosure of information by Company on its (a) websites, including all its divisions, subsidiaries and related companies (collectively, the "Websites"), (b) on various Third Party websites, and (c) to Company's other information collection, including the acquisition of customer information from third parties. Company is not responsible for the information collection or privacy practices of third party websites or applications. By reference, this Privacy Policy is incorporated into and is subject to the Terms of Use pertaining to the use of the website. Your use of the website and any individual information you provide via the website or through other official Company contact remains subject to this Privacy Policy as well as the applicable Terms and Conditions for use of the site or services and products contained thereon. By providing us with your individual information on our website or in the course of using our services, you consent to the transfer of your Personal Data and Sensitive Personal Data, and any other data we acquire about you from third-party service providers. 

### Information Collection, Use, and Dissemination practices.

This policy applies to Company's collection, use, storage and disclosure of information by Company on its, (a) websites, including all its parent companies, divisions, subsidiaries and related companies (collectively, the "Websites"), (b) on various third party websites, and (c) to Company's other information collection, including the transfer of opt-in customer lists from third parties, or the use of customer opt-in lists from third parties. Company is not responsible for the information collection or privacy practices of third party websites or applications.

### 1\. Collection of Information.

1.1. User Direct Information. Each time you provide transmit information via the Website, Company may obtain and collect personally identifiable information provided by you, including, but not limited to, your name, email address, mailing address and telephone or cell phone number. You may also provide us with information that, when combined with personally identifiable information, provides us with a better idea of who you are, including but not limited to your gender, birthday, marital status, and education level (collectively referred to as "individual information"). If you choose to access our website, use our services or purchase our products, we may require you to provide individual information as indicated on the forms throughout the site.

1.2. Survey Information. Company may collect information from you when you voluntarily complete a Company survey or questions on a website, order form, or a registration page either online by using the internet, offline by providing this information through the mail, in person or using a telephone. This information may be collected by surveys, order forms, or registration pages operated by third parties or by Company. This method of collection is collectively known as a "Survey." In such Surveys, Company or a third party may ask you to provide personal identifiable information including your name, email address, street address, zip code, telephone numbers (including cell phone numbers and carriers), birth date, gender, education and marital status, occupation, personal and online interests, and such other information as may be requested from time to time. Company may also collect such information concerning you from another source and uses that information in combination with information provided from the Websites. Completing the Surveys is completely voluntary, and you are under no obligation to provide Survey Information to Company or a third party.

1.3. Third Party Information. Company may collect information from you when you provide information to a third party and Company subsequently acquires or uses the information provided by the third party. Such information may include, but is not limited to, your name, email address, street address, zip code, telephone numbers (including cell phone numbers and carriers), birth date, gender, salary range, education and marital status, occupation, industry of employment, personal and online interests, and such other information as the you may have provided to the third party. When acquiring this information, Company seeks assurances from the third party that you agreed to provide and have such information acquired by Company. If you did not give express permission, or you would like to remove your permission, you may suppress all of your information by clicking here to enter an unsubscribe request.

1.4. Cookies, Web Beacons, and Other Info Collected Using Technology. Company currently uses cookie and web beacon technology to associate certain Internet-related information about you with information about you in its database. Additionally, Company may use other new and evolving sources of information in the future.

Cookies. "Cookies" are a feature on your browser software. If enabled, we may write cookies that may store small amounts of data on your computer about your visit to any of the pages of this Site. Cookies assist us in tracking which of our features appeal the most to you and what content you may have viewed on past visits. When you visit this site again, cookies can enable us to customize our content according to your preferences. We may use cookies to: keep track of the number of return visits to this site; accumulate and report aggregate, statistical information on website usage; deliver specific content to you based on your interests or past viewing history; save your password for ease of access to our Site. You can disable cookies, although the Site may not function properly for you. Your browser preferences can be modified to accept or reject all cookies, or request a notification when a cookie is set. You may read more about cookies at http://cookiecentral.com. In order to use all of the features and functionality of Company's websites, you need to accept cookies.

Web Beacons. A web beacon is a programming code that can be used to display an image on a web page, but can also be used to transfer your unique user identification to a database and associate you with previously acquired information about an individual in a database. This allows Company to track certain websites you visit. Web beacons are used to track online behavioral habits for marketing purposes to determine products or services you may be interested in. In addition to using web beacons on web pages, Company also uses web beacons in email messages sent to individuals listed in Company's database.

IP Addresses. Company automatically tracks certain information based upon your behavior on the site. We may use this information to do internal research on our users' demographics, interests, and behavior to better understand, protect and serve you and our community. This information may include the URL that you just came from (whether this URL is on the site or not), which URL you next go to (whether this URL is on the site or not), your computer browser information, and your IP address. Your Internet Protocol ("IP") is a unique Internet "address" which is assigned to you by your Internet Service Provider ("ISP"). For local area network ("LAN"), DSL, or cable modem users, an IP address may be permanently assigned to a particular computer. IP addresses are automatically logged by Web servers, collecting information about a user's traffic patterns. While the IP address does not identify an individual by name, it may, with the cooperation of the ISP, be used to locate and identify an individual using the Web. Your IP address can, however, reveal what geographic area you are connecting from, or which ISP you are using. Finally, other websites you visit have IP addresses, and we may collect the IP addresses of those websites and their pages.

Computer Profiles. Company may also collect and accumulate other anonymous data which will help us understand and analyze the Internet experience of our visitors. For instance, Company may accumulate visitor data relating to referring domain names, the type of browsers used, operating system software, screen resolutions, color capabilities, browser plug-ins, language settings, cookie preferences, search engine keywords and JavaScript enablement. When you provide us with Personal Identification Information, we are able to use such visitor data to identify you.

Data Analysis. Data Analysis technology may be employed from time to time if used by a Client of Company.

New Technology. The use of technology on the Internet, including cookies and web beacons, is rapidly developing. As a result, Company strongly encourages individuals to revisit this policy for any updates regarding its use of new technology.

1.5. No Information Collected from Children. Company will never knowingly collect any individual information about children under the age of 13. If Company obtains actual knowledge that it has collected individual information about a child under the age of 13, that information will be immediately deleted from its database. Because it does not collect such information, Company has no such information to use or to disclose to third parties. Company has designed this policy in order to comply with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act ("COPPA").

### 2\. Use of Individual Information.

2.0 General Use. The following paragraphs in Section Two describe how Company currently uses Individual Information, but Company may change or broaden its use at any time. As noted below, Company may update this policy from time to time. Company may use Individual Information to provide promotional offers to individuals by means of email advertising, telephone marketing, direct mail marketing, online banner advertising, and package stuffers, among other possible uses.

2.1. Request fulfillment. If you submit a request for services to obtain contact with a person or institution for a product or service offered through this website, we will share the individual information contained in your request form (such as your full name, address, telephone number, property location, self-assessed value, etc.) with third party service providers [hereinafter "service providers"] to contact you regarding your request. By submitting your request to LocalJobster.com, you have explicitly requested that these service providers contact you by telephone (where in your conversation may be recorded), email, or regular mail based on the Information you provided to us in order to process and fulfill your request, even if you have opted into the National Do Not Call List administered by the Federal Trade Commission, any state equivalent Do Not Call List, or the Do Not Call List of an internal company. If one of the service providers contacts you and you wish not to be contacted again by that service provider with respect to your inquiry, then you should specifically make a request to that service provider not to contact you again. Please note that the service providers may maintain the Information you provided whether you elect to use their services.

2.2. Email and Unsubscribe Policy. Company may also share your email address with service providers, as defined above, for the purpose of contacting you regarding a specific requests for information or a service. If email recipients wish to end their email subscription from a particular list, they need to follow the instructions at the end of each email message to unsubscribe from the particular list.

2.3. Targeted Advertising. Company may use individual information to target advertising to an individual. When an individual is using the Internet, Company uses Technology Information to associate an individual with that person's Individual Information, and Company attempts to show advertising for products and services in which the person has expressed an interest in the Surveys, indicated an interest by means of Technology Information, and otherwise. Company may, at its discretion, target advertising by using direct mail, telephones, cell phones, and other means of communication to provide promotional offers.

2.4. Wireless Addresses. If the e-mail address you provide to Company is a wireless e-mail address, you agree to receive messages at such address from Company or its business associates (unless and until you have elected not to receive such messages by following the instructions in the unsubscribe portion of this policy). You understand that your wireless carrier's standard rates apply to these messages. You represent that you are the owner or authorized user of the wireless device on which messages will be received, and that you are authorized to approve the applicable charges.

2.5. Short Message Service. Company may make available a service through which you can receive messages on your wireless device via short message service ("SMS Service"). You hereby agree that by inputting your wireless phone number you agree that Company may share your wireless number with third parties for the purpose of providing you with special promotion via text message. Data obtained from you in connection with this SMS service may include your name, address, cell phone number, your provider's name, and the date, time, and content of your messages. You represent that you are 18 years of age and the owner or authorized user of the wireless device on which messages will be received, and that you are authorized to approve the applicable charges. In addition to any fee of which you are notified your provider's standard messaging rates apply to our confirmation and all subsequent SMS correspondence. All charges are billed by and payable to your mobile service provider. Company will not be liable for any delays in the receipt of any SMS messages, as delivery is subject to effective transmission from your network operator. SMS message services are provided on an AS IS basis. Company may also obtain the date, time and content of your messages in the course of your use of the SMS Service. We will use the information we obtain in connection with our SMS Service in accordance with this Privacy Policy. If fees are charged to your wireless account invoice, we may provide your carrier with your applicable information in connection therewith. Your wireless carrier and other service providers may also collect data about your wireless device usage, and their practices are governed by their own policies.

Company may use individual information to provide the services you've requested, including services that display customized content and advertising. Company may also use individual information for auditing, research and analysis to operate and improve our technologies and services. Company may share aggregated and non individual information with third parties business associates. When Company uses business associates to assist Company in processing your individual information, Company requires that they comply with our Privacy Policy and any other appropriate confidentiality and security measures. Company may also share information with third parties, including but not limited to, when complying with legal process, preventing fraud or imminent harm, and ensuring the security of our network and services.

You may remove your information from Company's database. If you remove your information from Company's database it will no longer be used by Company for secondary purposes, disclosed to third parties, or used by Company or third parties to send promotional correspondence to you. You may remove your information by clicking here to enter an unsubscribe request and by responding with "STOP", "END", "QUIT" to the SMS text message you have received.

2.6. Use of Technology Information. Company uses Technology Information (1) to match a person's Survey Information and Third Party List Information to other categories of Individual Information to make and improve profiles of individuals, (2) to track a person's online browsing habits on the Internet, (3) to determine which areas of Company's websites are most frequently visited. This information helps Company to better understand the online habits of individuals so that Company can target advertising and promotions to them.

2.7. Profiles of Individuals. Company uses Individual Information to make a profile of an individual. A profile can be created by combining Survey Information and Third Party List Information with other sources of Individual Information such as information obtained from public databases.

2.8. Storage of Individual Information. Company stores the Individual Information in a database on its' computers. Our computers have security measures (such as a firewalls and password protection) in place to protect against the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under Company's control. Not withstanding such measures, Company cannot guarantee that its security measures will prevent its computers from being illegally accessed, and the Individual Information on them stolen or altered.

2.9. If you register on our site, you may receive live telephone calls from one or more of the callers listed below at the number you provided. Whether or not you receive any calls may depend on your answers to the survey questions that follow our registration page. You expressly waive all federal and state no-call restrictions with respect to such contact. You may opt out of receiving calls at any time by following the instructions provided by the caller or asking the caller to place you on its do-not-call list. Degree Services, College Center, College Coach, College Source, College Finder, Education Search, Education Source, Careers and College Connect, Education for Careers, Career Institute, Education Direct. 

### 3\. Privacy Practices of Third Parties.

3.1. Advertiser cookies and web beacons. Advertising agencies, advertising networks, and other companies who place advertisements on the website and on the internet generally may use their own cookies, web beacons, and other technology to collect information about individuals. Company does not control the use of such technology and Company has no responsibility for the use of such technology to gather information about you.

3.2. Links. The websites and email messages sometimes contain hypertext links to the websites of third parties. Company is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such other websites. Linked websites may contain links to websites maintained by third parties. Such links are provided for your convenience and reference only. Company does not operate or control in any respect any information, software, products or services available on such third party websites. The inclusion of a link to a website does not imply any endorsement of the services or the site, its contents, or its sponsoring organization.

3.3. Affiliations/Merger/Sale. Company further reserves the right to disclose, transfer or sell your individual information to companies who are affiliated with Company in Company's sole discretion. If Company changes ownership through an acquisition, merger, sale or other change of business status, it reserves the right to transfer or assign the right to use your Individual information collected from the Website.

4\. Foreign use of the Website. To the extent that you are accessing the Website while domiciled outside of the United States, you acknowledge that the Individual information you are providing Company is collected and stored in the United States and therefore consent to the transfer of information to and storage of the information outside of your domiciled country and in the United States.

5\. California User Consumer Rights.

In accordance with California Civil Code Sec. 1789.3, California resident users are entitled to know that they may file grievances and complaints with California Department of Consumer Affairs, 400 R Street, STE 1080, Sacramento, CA 95814; or by phone at 916-445-1254 or 800-952-5210; or by email to dca@dca.ca.gov. For more information about protecting your privacy, you may wish to visit: http://www.ftc.gov As a California resident, you have a legal right to request and receive in writing or by email the names and addresses of all such third parties who received your individual information during the previous calendar year and a list of the types of personally identifiable information disclosed to such third parties. To request such information, send an email to privacy@localjobster.com.

LocalJobster.com is committed to protecting the privacy of consumers. If you have any questions, comments or concerns regarding our Online Privacy Policy and its implementation, please do not hesitate to e-mail us at privacy@localjobster.com.

Close Privacy Policy
